widsets.com 2007-12-25

# WidSets

This Privacy Policy of "www.widsets.com" has been posted and is effective as of April 1st 2006. 

At Nokia your privacy is important and we are committed to protecting your personal data. As used in this Privacy Policy (this " **Policy** "), the term " **personal data** " means data such as: your name, mailing address, e-mail address, internet service provider, telephone number, or other personal information that may be supplied by you or collected about you according to applicable local legislation. We hope that this Policy helps you understand what kind of personal data, if any, we collect at this site and how we handle and use any such personal data after col-lection. 

## Applicability

By accessing and using this site, your use indicates your agreement with the terms of this Policy. **If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this site.**

This Policy is applicable to this and certain other our general informational web/mobile sites, but not necessarily all our web/mobile sites or web channels, for which special terms and conditions may apply as indicated. All our sites to which this Policy is applicable are collectively referred to as this " **site** ". Note that special use terms, or site or page specific terms (referred to as " **special terms** "), may apply to certain pages/services on this site, but the applicability of any such special terms will be expressly indicated. In the event of any inconsistency between any special terms and this Policy, the applicable special terms will prevail over the terms of this Policy. 

## Anonymous Use

In general, most of this site's pages are provided for informational purposes and you will be able to use this site without telling us who you are or providing us with any personal data about yourself. There are times, however, when in connection with your use of this site we may need information about you. 

## Personal Data Provided by You 

To respond to your questions, fulfill your requests or manage interactive customer programs, it may be necessary to ask for or obtain personal data. If you provide us with any personal data, we, including our affiliates and author-ized partners, may use it to respond to your requests, customize your user experience with us, determine your satisfaction with our products and/or services or contact you via mail, e-mail, mobile message or phone, or, in accordance with local law, contact you via the aforementioned channels to inform you of new products, services or promotions we may offer. **By providing information to us through this site, you acknowledge and consent to the collection, use of personally identifying information of the type and for the limited purposes described in this Policy.**

You are entitled to exercise your right of opposition, access, rectification or cancellation by contacting the data controller at the address set forth below. 

You expressly accept and give your consent that your personal data obtained in connection with your use of this site may be transferred, if permitted by applicable local legislation, across international borders, also outside the European Union to server locations supporting this site (including but not limited to transfers from those locations back to the country of your location) for operating and developing this site and our services, including transfers to our subcontractors or agents, as mentioned below, who perform tasks related to this site, or our services, or for the purposes of storing the data in relevant databases, which may be located in Finland or in any other country where we have operations. 

We may collect transactional information relating to your use of our products and Service and your other transactions with us. Your personal data may be processed for following purposes and to the extent necessary for that purpose: i) performance of this Agreement or fulfillment of your request; ii) to ensure the security of the Service iii) development and improvement of Nokia products and services; iv) communicating with you; v) personalizing our offering, for example to make recommendations and to display customized content and advertising on our website; vi) creation of statistical information; vii) compliance with mandatory legal requirements and/or in connection with law enforcement or other civil or criminal legal proceedings. 

We may combine your personal data collected in connection with your use of a particular Nokia product and/or service with personal data relating to your use of other Nokia products and/or services as well as with your other personal data. We may create statistics based on your personal data.” 

If you place an order for a product, request a service or submit content to this site, we may need to contact you for additional information required to process or fulfill your order and/or request. Unless compelled by applicable law or administrative or judicial order, we will not provide this information to a third party without your permission, except as necessary to process your order, fulfill your requests, manage interactive customer programs or, if you are a corporate user, enable administration of access and usage of this site by authorized personnel in your or-ganization. If allowed by applicable local legislation, we may also exchange information between our affiliated (related) companies for the purposes mentioned in this Policy. 

**Because we are committed to protecting your privacy, we do not engage in the practice of selling or trad-ing personal data to other companies for promotional purposes.**

Please note, that if we decide to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganise our businesses in some countries, this may involve us disclosing personal data to prospective or actual purchasers, or receiving it from sellers, or their advisers, being these entities subject to confidentiality rules and not having the power to use that data to other purposes then those to which the data has been initially collected. 

## Usage of Subcontractors

We may use subcontractors to provide some products or services to you. We also may need to share your per-sonal data with these subcontractors so that they can provide services to us. Our subcontractors are not permitted to use such personal data for any other purposes and we impose confidentiality requirements on their services. 

## Visitor Identification - Usage of "Cookies"

From time to time, information may be placed on your computer to improve this site and our services for you. This information is commonly referred to as a "cookie", which many web sites use. Cookies are pieces of data stored on your computer's hard drive or browser, and not on this site. They typically enable collection of certain information about your computer, including your internet protocol address, your computer's operating system, your browser type and the address of any referring sites. 

The use of cookies provides benefits to you, such as eliminating the need for you to enter your password frequently during a session, or, where applicable, re-enter items you place in a shopping cart from visit to visit if you do not finish a transaction on an earlier visit. By showing how and when our visitors use this site or other our sites, the use of cookies allows us to continue to improve the sites. If you do not wish to receive cookies, or want to be notified of when they are placed, you may set your web browser to do so, if your browser so permits. Please understand that if cookies are turned off, you may not be able to view certain parts of this site that may enhance your visit. Some of our business partners whose content is linked to or from this site may also use cookies. How-ever, we have no access to or control over these cookies. This site also makes use of cookies for website traffic analysis and anonymous demographic profiling. 

## Security

We have endeavored to take commercially reasonable measures to prevent unauthorized access to and improper use of your personal data submitted to us via your use of this site. For example, we use encryption technology when collecting financial personal data such as credit card information. If this site supports on-line transactions, it will use an industry standard security measure, such as the one available through "Secure Sockets Layer" ("SSL"), to protect the confidentiality and security of online transactions. If used, industry standard security measures like SSL authentication ensure that credit card information, as well as other personal data submitted as part of the buying process, is reasonably safe from third party interception. 

While there are always risks associated with providing personal data, whether in person, by phone or via the internet or other technologies, and no system of technology is completely safe or "tamper"/"hacker" proof, we have endeavored to take reasonable precautions which are appropriate to the nature of the information to prevent and minimize such risks in connection with your use of this site. 

## Accuracy of Collected Data

We will on our own initiative, or at your request, free of charge, replenish, rectify or erase any incomplete, inaccurate or outdated personal data retained by us in connection with the operation of this site. Please consult the contact information posted below on this page, if any, or elsewhere on this site to determine how best to con-tact us to update and/or review your personal data and/or opt out of receiving marketing communications from us. 

## Minors

Our policy is to request that " **Minors** " (the age of Minors is determined by local law where you reside) do not make purchases or engage in other legal acts on this site without the consent of a parent or legal guardian, unless permitted by applicable local law. 

## External Links

This site may contain links to other sites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of any other sites. We recommend that you read the privacy policies of such sites. 

## Data Controller

The Controller of the database of your personal data shall be Nokia Corporation of Keilalahdentie 4, 02150 Espoo, Finland. 

## Changes to this Policy

We may from time to time change this Policy or change, modify or withdraw access to this site at any time with or without notice. However, if this Policy is changed in a material, adverse way, we will post a notice advising of such change at the beginning of this Policy and on this site's home page for 30 days. We recommend that you re-visit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy. 

Copyright © Nokia 2005. All rights reserved.
